zegist.com 2015-04-21

# Privacy Policy - Zegist Magazine

### INTRODUCTION

Zegist Magazine Limited (“Zegist” or “we”) wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information collected through services such as websites, mobile sites, applications (“apps”), and widgets. By using Zegist, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is effective from 17th June 2014

As set forth in our Terms of Use, the Zegist Magazine is for a general audience, are not targeted to children, and do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age.

This Privacy Policy applies to all users, including both those who use Zegist without being registered with or subscribing to our magazine and those who have registered with or subscribed to a Zegist Service. This Privacy Policy applies to Zegist Magazine and use of your personal information (i.e., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address). It also describes generally Zegist’s practices for handling non-personal information (for example, interests, demographics and services usage).

### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

Zegist and our service providers collect the following information from and about you:

Registration Information is the information you submit to register for a Zegist Service, for example, to create an account, post comments, receive a newsletter, or enter a contest or sweepstakes. Registration Information may include, for example, name, email address, gender and birthday.

Public Information and Posts consist of comments or content that you post to the magazine and the information about you that accompanies those posts or content, which may include a name, user name, comments, likes, status, profile information and picture. Public Information and Posts are always public, which means they are available to everyone and may be displayed in search results on external search engines.

Information from Social Media. If you access or log-in to a Zegist Service through a social media service or connect a Zegist Service to a social media service, the information we collect may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that social media service, any information or content you have permitted the social media service to share with us, such as your profile picture, email address or friends lists, and any information you have made public in connection with that social media service. When you access the Zegist Services through social media services or when you connect a Zegist Service to social media services, you are authorizing Zegist to collect, store, and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Activity Information. When you access and interact with the Zegist Services, we may collect certain information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to the Zegist Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer, device, and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access the Zegist Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device, geolocation data, or other transactional information for that device.

Cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe Flash technology including cookies) are comprised of small bits of data that often include a de-identified or anonymous unique identifier. Websites, apps and other services send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that service. These technologies may also be used to collect and store information about your usage of the Zegist Services, such as pages you have visited, content you have viewed, search queries you have run and advertisements you have seen. If Zegist wishes to combine your personal information with information we obtain through these technologies in order to determine what messages Zegist provides to you, we will obtain your express affirmative consent.

Third parties that support the Zegist Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as allowing you to share content or tracking aggregate Zegist Services usage statistics, may also use these technologies to collect similar information. Zegist does not control these third-party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of third parties using such technologies. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see www.aboutads.info/consumers, and to opt-out of such ad networks’ and services’ advertising practices, go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

Like many other Web sites, www.zegist.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Zegist does use cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information. Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features, content or personalization available through the Zegist Services.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.zegist.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Information from Other Sources. We may supplement the information we collect with information from other sources, such as publicly available information from social media services, commercially available sources and information from our Zegist Affiliates or business partners.

### USE AND DISCLOSURE

We use the information we collect from and about you to provide the Zegist Services and features to you, including: to measure and improve those Zegist Services and features; to improve your experience with both online and off-line Zegist Services by delivering content you will find relevant and interesting, including advertising and marketing messages; to allow you to comment on content and to provide you with customer support and to respond to inquiries. When the information collected from or about you does not identify you as a specific person, we may use that information for any purpose or share it with third parties.

We use the information we collect from and about you for these additional purposes:

To allow service providers to assist us in providing and managing the Zegist Services. Zegist may make your information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide the Zegist Services.

To allow social sharing functionality. If you log in with or connect a social media service account with Zegist Services, we may share your user name, picture, and likes, as well as your activities and comments with other Zegist Services users and with your friends associated with your social media service. We may also share the same information with the social media service provider. By logging in with or connecting your Zegist Services account with a social media service, you are authorizing us to share information we collect from and about you with the social media service provider, other users and your friends and you understand that the social media service’s use of the shared information will be governed by the social media service’s privacy policy. If you do not want your personal information shared in this way, please do not connect your social media service account with your Zegist Services account and do not participate in social sharing on Zegist Services.

To deliver relevant advertisements. Zegist and our service providers may use the information we collect from and about you to deliver relevant ads to you when you use the Zegist Services or another service. As noted above, third-party advertising networks and advertisers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred interests, aggregated information, and activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see www.aboutads.info, and to opt-out of such advertising networks’ and services’ advertising practices, go to [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices). Our principal advertising partner is Google.

DoubleClick DART Cookie: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.zegist.com](http://www.zegist.com/). Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.zegist.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

To contact you. Zegist may periodically send promotional materials or notifications related to the Zegist Services. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, you can follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of, such as notifications of changes to the Zegist Services or policies. If you have installed a mobile app and you wish to stop receiving push notifications, you can change the settings either on your mobile device or through the app.

To share with our Zegist Affiliates. Zegist may share your information with Zegist affiliates (“Affiliated Companies”) for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. Users who visit Affiliated Companies’ services should still refer to their separate privacy policies, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy.

To share with business partners. Zegist may share your information with business partners to permit them to send you marketing communications consistent with your choices.

To protect the rights of Zegist and others. There may be instances when Zegist may disclose your information, including situations where Zegist has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect, enforce, or defend the legal rights, privacy, safety, or property of Zegist, our Zegist Affiliates or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements and our terms of use); (ii) protect the safety, privacy, and security of users of the Zegist Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; (iv) comply with the law or legal process; or (v) respond to requests from public and government authorities.

To complete a merger or sale of assets. If Zegist sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, Zegist may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

### SECURITY

Zegist uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification.

### USER ACCESS AND CONTROL

If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact us. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

We give you many choices regarding our use and disclosure of your personal information for marketing purposes. You may opt-out from:

Receiving electronic communications from us: If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving these marketing-related emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in the email.

Cancelling your account. To cancel your account, email mailto:hello@zegist.com, subject, “Delete My Account” and include the email address that you registered your account with (if different from the email address you’re sending the email from). Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in some circumstances – where, for example, you have shared information with a third-party application or web site. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others, and there may be a delay in the removal of the content from elsewhere on the Internet and from search engines.

### OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION

Updates to Privacy Policy. Zegist may modify this Privacy Policy. Please look at the Effective Date at the top of this Privacy Policy to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Zegist Services. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that expand our rights to use the personal information we have already collected from you, we will notify you and provide you with a choice about our future use of that information.

Location of Data. The Zegist Services are hosted in and managed from the United States. If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information processed in the United States. United States data protection and other relevant laws may not be the same as those in your jurisdiction. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

Linked Services. The Zegist Services may also be linked to sites operated by unaffiliated companies, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by unaffiliated companies. Zegist is not responsible for the privacy practices of unaffiliated companies, and once you leave the Zegist Services or click an advertisement you should check the applicable privacy policy of the other service.

Data Retention. We will retain your information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law.

Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information from your account may remain viewable in some circumstances where, for example, you have shared information with social media or other services. Because of the nature of caching technology, your account may not be instantly inaccessible to others. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancelation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. It is not always possible to completely remove or delete all of your information due to technical constraints, contractual, financial or legal requirements.

Sensitive Information. We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive personal information (such as social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Zegist Services or otherwise.

### CONTACT US

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please use our [contact form](http://zegist.com/contact/ "Contact")

Email: [hello@zegist.com](mailto:hello@zegist.com)
